<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Stranger Society</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Stranger Society</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:11:22 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Society</title>
      <link>/authors/example-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:11:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/example-author/</guid>
      <description>What is Stranger Society? It’s a journey of introspection, embracing one of the oldest spirits in making sense of the world, internal and external, and communicating it with fellow beings; The spirit of storytelling.
It’s a community for those who choose, willingly, to embrace the stranger’s voice that’s within all of us.
The voice that questions and shakes the whole foundation of our existence, beliefs and faith.
The voice that intensifies in our solitude, feeding on our depression, anger and pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/hugo-authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/hugo-authors/</guid>
      <description>Vestibulum vel arcu Donec interdum justo sed posuere imperdiet. Quisque nec mauris eu erat mattis egestas in vitae nisl. Sed nisl augue, congue sed quam quis, tempor tempus nibh. Pellentesque accumsan in quam a interdum. Morbi iaculis venenatis lacinia. Mauris quis nisl vitae nisi mollis placerat id vel ligula. Integer vitae arcu ac leo iaculis rhoncus id vitae dolor. Fusce quis nisl tincidunt, vulputate dolor quis, mollis massa. Donec congue velit at risus cursus, eu auctor dolor rhoncus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
